A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82) FA209
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (A81), 1874-2003; 7; 163.49 Cubic Feet 449 containers. Boxes 652-1076; Document boxes 652-1076.
  - Closed Materials Separated from Project Files RG1.7 (A81) (Box 1072, Folder 4351A-5577A)
    - City University o New York - Muller, 1973 (Box 696, Folder 4654A)
    - National Planning Association - Canadian - American Relations, 1994 (Box 724, Folder 4841A)
    - University of Pittsburgh - U. S. - Cuban Relations Conference, 1975 (Box 732, Folder 4902A)
    - World Without War Council - International Conflict and American Organizations Project, 1975 (Box 735, Folder 4922A)
    - Pollack, J. D., 1976 (Box 747, Folder 5004A)
    - University of Alabama - Beck - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 754, Folder 5041A)
    - Cornell University - Young, 1975 (Box 754, Folder 5042A)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Weisz, 1970 (Box 755, Folder 5044A)
    - American Geographical Society - Vegetation Maps, 1975 (Box 761, Folder 5084A)
    - American Indian Lawyer Training Project - Fellowships, 1974 (Box 762, Folder 5092A)
    - Blackwell, Barbara, 1977 (Box 765, Folder 5110A)
    - Bowling Green State University - Thailand Labor Study, 1975 (Box 765, Folder 5112A)
    - Center for Educational Leadership - Management Training, 1973, 1976 (Box 767, Folder 5130A)
    - Collier County Conservancy, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 774, Folder 5158A)
    - Colorado State University - Global Water Law, 1974 (Box 774, Folder 5163A)
    - Commission on Private Philanthropy and Public Needs, 1975-1976 (Box 776, Folder 5171A)
    - Duke University - Student Assistance, 1965-1966 (Box 784, Folder 5230A)
    - Edison Little Rive Self Help Community Council, 1976 (Box 784, Folder 5232A)
    - Emory University - Student Assistance, 1965 (Box 785, Envelope 5237A)
    - Fairfield University Watershed Project, 1976 (Box 785, Folder 5238A)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Goswami
      - 1977 (Box 793, Folder 5302A)
      - 1975 (Box 796, Folder 5321A)
    - Merrill - Palmer Institute - Early Childhood Development, 1974-1977 (Box 800, Folder 5341A)
    - Michigan State University - Water Reclamation
      - 1973 (Box 800, Folder 5345A)
      - Supplementary Material, 1974 (Box 803, Folder 5355A)
    - Minneapolis - Education - Dunham, 1976 (Box 805, Folder 5368A)
    - National Committee for Citizens in Education - Leadership Development, 1975 (Box 807, Folder 5389A)
    - National Alchemy Institute - Fisher Conference, 1975 (Box 809, Folder 5401A)
    - New York Botanical Gardens - Contraceptive Use of Plants, 1975 (Box 810, Folder 5406A)
    - Transnational Family Research Institute - Abortion Research Reference (Box 826, Folder 5519)
      - 1975 (Box 826, Folder 5519A)
      - 1976 (Box 826, Folder 5520A)
    - University of California - Environmental Ethics, Santa Barbara, 1975 (Box 828, Folder 5540A)
    - University of California - Water Quality, Los Angeles - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 831, Folder 5561A)
    - University of Colorado - Selenium, 1976 (Box 832, Folder 5571A)
    - University of Illinois - Nitrogen Studies, 1971 (Box 833, Folder 5577A)
- Projects (A82), 1944-2002; 8; 164.55 Cubic Feet Boxes 1077-1506. 392 letter-sized boxes, 24 legal-sized boxes, 6 half-letter-sized boxes, 6 half-legal-sized boxes, one 21x17 short oversized box, one 18x14 short oversized box, and 3 containers; Document boxes 1077-1506.
  Files transferred to RAC by the Rockefeller Foundation, August 1982-May 1983.
  - International, 100; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - International Press Institute (Box 1077, Folder 7236)
  - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center, 105; 2.28 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes
    - Personnel (CIMMYT) only, 1967-1970 (Box 1077, Folder 7237-7238)
    - Spring-Winter Wheat, 1967-1978, 1982 (Box 1077, Folder 7239-7240)
    - Socio-Economic Conference, 1977-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 1077, Folder 7241, Box 1078, Folder 7242)
    - Socio-Economic Conference - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 1078, Folder 7243)
    - Socio-Economic Conference - Supplementary Material, 1979 May 7-11 (Box 1078, Folder 7244)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramient de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - International Organizations, 103
      - United Nations Development Program - Agricultural Economics, 1975, 1980, 1982 (Box 1078, Folder 7245)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramient de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - North Africa Region, 485
      - Wheat Improvement, 1966-1976, 1980, 1982 (Box 1078, Folder 7246, Box 1079, Folder 7247-7251)
    - Centro Internacional de Mejoramient de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) - Near East Region, 804
      - Oregon State University - Wheat Improvement, 1969-1982 (Box 1080, Folder 7252-7257, Box 1081, Folder 7258)
      - Oregon State University - Wheat Improvement - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 1081, Folder 7259)
      - Oregon State University - Wheat Improvement - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975, 1978 (Box 1081, Folder 7260-7262)
      - Wheat Improvement - Personnel, 1968-1970, 1980, 1982 (Box 1081, Folder 7263)
      - Wheat Improvement - Personnel, 1970-1972 (Box 1081, Folder 7264)
      - Wheat Improvement - Personnel, 1972-1976 (Box 1082, Folder 7265)
      - Wheat Improvement - Personnel - Supplies and Equipment, 1970-1974 (Box 1082, Folder 7266)
      - Wheat Trainees, 1970-1979 1982 (Box 1082, Folder 7267)
  - Trypanosomiasis and East Coast Fever, 106; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Task Force, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1082, Folder 7268-7269, Box 1083, Folder 7270-7274, Box 1084, Folder 7275)
    - Task Force - Post Cards, 1979 (Box 1084, Folder 7276)
    - Trypanosomiasis & East Coast Fever, 1973-1982 (Box 1084, Folder 7277)
  - International Potato Program, 107; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
    - IPP - Peru, 331
      - International Potato Program, 1971-1983 (Box 1084, Folder 7278-7279, Box 1085, Folder 7280-7285, Box 1086, Folder 7286-7287)
      - International Potato Program - Evaluation, 1971, 1973, 1975-1979 (Box 1086, Folder 7288)
      - International Potato Program - Supplementary Material, 1970-1979 (Box 1086, Folder 7289-7291)
      - Personnel, 1972-1980, 1982 (Box 1086, Folder 7292)
      - Organizations - Supplementary Material, 1980-1981 (Box 1086, Folder 7293)
      - Werge, 1974-1982 (Box 1087, Folder 7294-7298)
      - Werge - Evaluation, 1977-1981 (Box 1087, Folder 7299)
  - International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT), 110; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
    - Animal Sciences, 1967-1982 (Box 1088, Folder 7300-7302)
    - Animal Sciences - Supplementary Material, 1967-1969, 1973-1974 (Box 1088, Folder 7303-7305)
    - Bean Diseases - Monograph, 1972-1982 (Box 1089, Folder 7306)
    - Bean Diseases - Monograph - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 1089, Folder 7307)
    - Headquarters Development, 1968-1980, 1982 (Box 1089, Folder 7308-7312, Box 1090, Folder 7313)
    - Headquarters Development - Evaluation, 1974-1979 (Box 1090, Folder 7314)
    - Supplies and Equipment, 1967-1974 (Box 1090, Folder 7315-7318)
    - Institute of Agriculture Science and Technology (ICTA), 1973-1982; 319 (Box 1090, Folder 7319, Box 1091, Folder 7320-7324, Box 1092, Folder 7325-7330, Box 1093, Folder 7331)
    - Institute of Agriculture Science and Technology (ICTA) - Evaluation, 1976-1983; 319 (Box 1093, Folder 7332)
    - Institute of Agriculture Science and Technology (ICTA) - Supplementary Material, 1971-1982; 319 (Box 1093, Folder 7333-7337, Box 1094, Folder 7338-7344, Box 1095, Folder 7345-7350)
    - Donation of Equipment, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1096, Folder 7351)
    - Personnel, 1972-1974, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1096, Folder 7352)
  - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases (ILRAD), 112; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Parasites Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 1096, Folder 7353)
    - Tissue Culture Conference, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1096, Folder 7354)
    - Tissue Culture Conference - Evaluation, 1978-1980, 1986 (Box 1096, Folder 7355)
    - Tissue Culture Conference - Supplementary Material, 1979 (Box 1096, Folder 7356)
  - International Livestock Centre for Africa (ILCA), 113; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Task Force, 1971, 1980, 1982 (Box 1096, Folder 7357-7358, Box 1097, Folder 7359)
    - Task Force - Supplementary Material, 1971 Oct. 15 (Box 1097, Folder 7360)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 115; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Personnel, 1964-1980, 1982 (Box 1097, Folder 7361-7365)
    - Publicity and Reports no material (Box 1098, Folder 7366)
      File
      No Material Content
  - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), 116; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Personnel - Doherty, 1975-1980, 1982 (Box 1098, Folder 7367-7368)
    - Personnel - Doherty - Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 1098, Folder 7369)
    - Personnel - Doherty - Supplementary Material, 1978, 1981 (Box 1098, Folder 7370-7372)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 14.95 Cubic Feet 40 containers
    - African Higher Education Conference, 1977-1978, 1982 (Box 1099, Folder 7373)
    - African Higher Education Conference, 1978 (Box 1099, Folder 7374)
    - African Higher Education Conference - Supplementary Material, 1977-1979 (Box 1099, Folder 7375-7378, Box 1100, Folder 7379)
    - Agricultural Production & the Rural Poor Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 1100, Folder 7380)
    - Agricultural Research System Conference, 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1100, Folder 7381-7382)
    - Agricultural Staff Training Conference, 1977-1979 1982 (Box 1100, Folder 7383)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Africa Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 1100, Folder 7384)
    - Animal and Plant Pathogen Vectors Conference, 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1100, Folder 7385-7386, Box 1101, Folder 7387-7391, Box 1102, Folder 7392-7394)
    - Atlantic World Economic Policies - Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1102, Folder 7395)
    - Automation and Industrial Workers Conference, 1975-1978, 1982 (Box 1102, Folder 7396)
    - Automation and Industrial Workers Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1102, Folder 7397)
    - Biochemical Nomenclature Conference, 1977, 1979-1983 (Box 1102, Folder 7398)
    - Biomedical Communications Conference, 1977, 1979, 1982 (Box 1103, Folder 7399)
    - Biomedical Communications Conference - Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 1103, Folder 7400)
    - Black American and African Universities, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1103, Folder 7401)
    - Black Communication Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 1103, Folder 7402)
    - Brain and Dreaming Conference, 1977, 1980, 1982, 1986, 1988 (Box 1103, Folder 7404)
    - Canada and European Security Conference, 1978-1982 (Box 1103, Folder 7405)
    - Carnegie Endowment - Arab Conference (not held), 1977-1978, 1982 (Box 1103, Folder 7406)
    - Chile and Democracy Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1103, Folder 7407)
    - Chorionic Gonadotropin Conference, 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1104, Folder 7408)
    - Clinical Research in Developing Countries Conference, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1104, Folder 7409)
    - Collectivity and Individuality Conference, 1977, 1979-1982, 1984 (Box 1104, Folder 7410)
    - Commission on United States Policy Toward Africa Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1104, Folder 7411)
    - Contemporary Geography Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1104, Folder 7412)
    - Coping and Health Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1104, Folder 7413)
    - Coptic Encyclopedia Conference, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1104, Folder 7414-7415)
    - Crisis Management Conference, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1104, Folder 7416)
    - Crisis Management Conference - Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 1104, Folder 7417)
    - Downy Mildew Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1105, Folder 7418-7419)
    - Educational Development Conference, 1971-1982 (Box 1105, Folder 7420-7422, Box 1106, Folder 7423-7427, Box 1107, Folder 7428-7432, Box 1108, Folder 7433-7437, Box 1109, Folder 7438-7440)
    - Educational Development Conference - Supplementary Material, 1970-1982 (Box 1109, Folder 7441-7442, Box 1110, Folder 7443-7448, Box 1111, Folder 7449-7453)
    - European Communities Politics Conference, 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1112, Folder 7454)
    - European Communities Politics Conference - Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 1112, Folder 7455)
    - European Languages Literature Conference, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1112, Folder 7456)
    - Food Corps and Rural Development Conference, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1112, Folder 7457-7459)
    - Government Services Comparisons Conference, 1977, 1980-1982 (Box 1113, Folder 7460)
    - Health and Population in Developing Countries Conference, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1113, Folder 7461-7463)
    - Health and Population in Developing Countries Conference - Supplementary Material, 1977-1979 (Box 1113A, Folder 7463A, 7463B, 7463C, 7463D)
    - Human Rights and Developing Nations Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1113A, Folder 7464-7465, Box 1114, Folder 7466)
    - Human Rights and Developing Nations Conference - Supplementary Material, 1979 June (Box 1114, Folder 7467-7469)
    - Human Rights Organizations Conference, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1114, Folder 7470)
    - Human Rights Organizations Conference - Supplementary Material, 1979 October (Box 1114, Folder 7471)
    - Humanities and Education for Development Conference, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1115, Folder 7472)
    - Humanities and Education for Development Conference - Supplementary Material, 1966-1974, 1977-1979 (Box 1115, Folder 7473-7475)
    - Images of Order and Disorder Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 1115, Folder 7476)
    - International Economics Conference, 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1115, Folder 7477)
    - International House (NYC) - Alumni Conference, 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1115, Folder 7478)
    - International Library Organizations Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1115, Folder 7479)
    - Judiciary and Economic Integration Conference, 1977-1979, 1982-1983 (Box 1116, Folder 7480)
    - Language and Power Conference, 1977,1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1116, Folder 7481)
    - Leadership and Government Performance Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1116, Folder 7482)
    - Makerere University - Donors' Conference, 1978-1982 (Box 1116, Folder 7483-7484)
    - Makerere University - Donors' Conference - Supplementary Material, 1979-1980 (Box 1116, Folder 7485)
    - Migration Studies Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1116, Folder 7486)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Antarctic Resource Management Conference, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1117, Folder 7487-7489)
    - Nuclear Energy Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1117, Folder 7490)
    - Nuclear Proliferation Conference, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1117, Folder 7491)
    - Nutrition and Immunology Conference, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1117, Folder 7492)
    - Nutrition and Nursing Education Conference, 1977, 1979, 1982 (Box 1117, Folder 7493)
    - Nutrition and Parasitic Inspections Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1117, Folder 7494)
    - People and Politics Conference, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1117, Folder 7495)
    - Pest Control Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1118, Folder 7496)
    - Plant Disease Management Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1118, Folder 7497-7501)
    - Plant Disease Management Conference - Supplementary Material, 1981 (Box 1118, Folder 7502)
    - Primer in Coping with the Biomedical Literatures Conference[unreadable] (not held), 1977-1980 (Box 1119, Folder 7503)
    - Property Law Rights in the Near and Middle East Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1119, Folder 7504)
    - Psychosocial Factors and Health Conference, 1977, 1980, 1982 (Box 1119, Folder 7505)
    - Psychosocial Factors and Health Conference - Supplementary Material, 1979, 1981 (Box 1119, Folder 7506)
    - Quality Based Libraries for Medical Schools (in less developed countries) Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1119, Folder 7507)
    - Quality Based Libraries for Medical Schools (in less developed countries) Conference - Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 1119, Folder 7508)
    - Race and International Relations Conference (cancelled), 1976-1977, 1982 (Box 1119, Folder 7509)
    - Rural Development Conference, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1119, Folder 7510)
    - Rural Economy in Eastern Europe Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1119, Folder 7511)
    - Russian Novel Conference, 1976-1984 (Box 1119, Folder 7512)
    - Scholars - Abraham, A., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 1120, Folder 7513)
    - Scholars - Abraham, H., 1975-1978, 1982, 1987-1989 (Box 1120, Folder 7514)
    - Scholars - Adams, L., 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1120, Folder 7515)
    - Scholars - Aldridge, A., 1972, 1977 1980-1981, 1995 (Box 1120, Folder 7516)
    - Scholars - Altschul, Siri von Reis, 1977-1983 (Box 1120, Folder 7517)
    - Scholars - Amoia, A., 1977-1982 (Box 1120, Folder 7518)
    - Scholars - Bardach, J., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1120, Folder 7519)
    - Scholars - Barkin, E., 1974-1984 (Box 1120, Folder 7520)
    - Scholars - Baron, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1120, Folder 7521)
    - Scholars - Beckerman, W., 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1120, Folder 7522)
    - Scholars - Bienen, H., 1977-1982 (Box 1120, Folder 7523)
    - Scholars - Bindra (did not go), 1977, 1980-1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7524)
    - Scholars - Binion, R., 1977-1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7525)
    - Scholars - Blegvad, B., 1977-1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7526)
    - Scholars - Blegvad, M., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7527)
    - Scholars - Block, J., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7528)
    - Scholars - Blotner, J., 1974-1982, 1984-1988 (Box 1121, Folder 7529)
    - Scholars - Bonomi, P., 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7530)
    - Scholars - Boruch, R., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7531)
    - Scholars - Bowen (did not go), 1977-1979, 1982-1983 (Box 1121, Folder 7532)
    - Scholars - Boyers, R., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7533)
    - Scholars - Bremner, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1121, Folder 7534)
    - Scholars - Campbell, A. (did not go), 1977, 1980-1982 (Box 1122, Folder 7535)
    - Scholars - Cazorla, J., 1977, 1979-1984 (Box 1122, Folder 7536)
    - Scholars - Chadwick, O., 1976-1982 (Box 1122, Folder 7537)
    - Scholars - Chalmers, J., 1977-1980, 1982, 1993, 2002 (Box 1122, Folder 7538)
    - Scholars - Chaves, M., 1977, 1979-1983 (Box 1122, Folder 7539)
    - Scholars - Christol, C., 1977-1983, 1997 (Box 1122, Folder 7540)
    - Scholars - Claire, W., 1977, 1979-1986 (Box 1122, Folder 7541)
    - Scholars - Clark, B., 1977, 1979-1980, 1983 (Box 1122, Folder 7542)
    - Scholars - Clements, R., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1122, Folder 7543)
    - Scholars - Climent, C., 1977-1982 (Box 1122, Folder 7544)
    - Scholars - Cohen, E., 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1122, Folder 7545)
    - Scholars - Collins, R., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7546)
    - Scholars - Dallin, A., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7547)
    - Scholars - DeBary, T., 1977-1983, 1986 (Box 1123, Folder 7548)
    - Scholars - DeGroot, A., 1977-1979, 1982-1983 (Box 1123, Folder 7549)
    - Scholars - Deutsch, K. (did not go), 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7550)
    - Scholars - Douglas, M. (did not go), 1976-1977, 1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7551)
    - Scholars - Drescher, S., 1977-1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7552)
    - Scholars - Dreyfus, F., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7553)
    - Scholars - Edel, L., 1968, 1971, 1973, 1975-1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7554)
    - Scholars - Edwards, D., 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7555)
    - Scholars - Elberg, S., 1977, 1979-1983 (Box 1123, Folder 7556)
    - Scholars - Elias, V., 1977-1984, 1992 (Box 1123, Folder 7557)
    - Scholars - Erb, D., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7558)
    - Scholars - Evers, Hans-Ulrich, 1977-1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7559)
    - Scholars - Fabricant, J., 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7560)
    - Scholars - Ferris, D., 1977-1982 (Box 1123, Folder 7561)
    - Scholars - Fennell, J., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1124, Box 7562)
    - Scholars - Flexner, J., 1977, 1979-1982, 1984 (Box 1124, Folder 7563)
    - Scholars - Fraser, 1975-1980, 1982, 1989-1980 (Box 1124, Folder 7564)
    - Scholars - Frears, J., 1977-1982, 1990-1991 (Box 1124, Folder 7565)
    - Scholars - Freeman, H., 1977-1980, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 1124, Folder 7566)
    - Scholars - Gandi, K., 1977-1982 (Box 1124, Folder 7567)
    - Scholars - Gaudon, Jean and Sheila, 1964, 1977-1980, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 1124, Folder 7568)
    - Scholars - Glazer, N., 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1124, Folder 7569)
    - Scholars - Greenberg, Jack and Deborah, 1968, 1977-1982, 1989-2000 (Box 1124, Folder 7570)
    - Scholars - Grumbach, D., 1977-1982 (Box 1124, Folder 7571)
    - Scholars - Gulek, K., 1977-1982 (Box 1124, Folder 7572)
    - Scholars - Hammond, T., 1977-1982, 1990-1991 (Box 1125, Folder 7573)
    - Scholars - Harrison, B., 1977-1983 (Box 1125, Folder 7574)
    - Scholars - Henrich, D., 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1125, Folder 7575)
    - Scholars - Hershlag, Z., 1969-1972, 1977-1982, 1984, 1987 (Box 1125, Folder 7576)
    - Scholars - Hiller, G., 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1125, Folder 7577)
    - Scholars - Hoadley, S. (did not go), 1977, 1980, 1982 (Box 1125, Folder 7578)
    - Scholars - Hofmann, A., 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1125, Folder 7579)
    - Scholars - Hofsten, E., 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1125, Folder 7580)
    - Scholars - Howard, D., 1977-1982 (Box 1125, Folder 7581)
    - Scholars - Hyman, H., 1977-1983 (Box 1125, Folder 7582)
    - Scholars - Inez, C., 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1125, Folder 7583)
    - Scholars - Jelliffe, D., 1976-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 1125, Folder 7584)
    - Scholars - Jenkin, L., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1126, Folder 7585)
    - Scholars - Jennings, F., 1971, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1126, Folder 7586)
    - Scholars - Johnson, E., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1126, Folder 7587)
    - Scholars - Jose, F., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1985, 1991 (Box 1126, Folder 7588)
    - Scholars - Jung, A., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1126, Folder 7589)
    - Scholars - Kattenburg, P., 1977-1983, 1992 (Box 1126, Folder 7590)
    - Scholars - Katz, A., 1977-1983, 1989-1990 (Box 1126, Folder 7591)
    - Scholars - Kessler, J., 1977-1983, 1996-1997 (Box 1126, Folder 7592)
    - Scholars - Kogan, N., 1977-1982 (Box 1126, Folder 7593)
    - Scholars - Lambert, W., 1977, 1979-1982,1989-1990 (Box 1126, Folder 7594)
    - Scholars - Lande, C., 1977-1982 (Box 1126, Folder 7595)
    - Scholars - Lapidus, G., 1977-1982 (Box 1126, Folder 7596)
    - Scholars - Lesemann, F., 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 1127, Folder 7597)
    - Scholars - Loewenberg, P., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982, 1990 (Box 1127, Folder 7598)
    - Scholars - Louis, R., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 1127, Folder 7599)
    - Scholars - Low, D., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 1127, Folder 7600)
    - Scholars - Lynton, H., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1127, Folder 7601)
    - Scholars - Lynton, R., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1127, Folder 7602)
    - Scholars - Lyons (Box 1127, Folder 7603)
    - Scholars - Mackesy, P., 1977, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 1128, Folder 7604)
    - Scholars - Mangone, G., 1975-1979, 1982, 1991 (Box 1128, Folder 7605)
    - Scholars - Martin, Rex, 1977-1980 1982 (Box 1128, Folder 7606)
    - Scholars - Martin, Robert, 1977-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 1128, Folder 7607)
    - Scholars - Matthews, M., 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1128, Folder 7608)
    - Scholars - McGrade, A., 1977, 1979-1982, 1990 (Box 1128, Folder 7609)
    - Scholars - McManners, J., 1977-1979, 1982-1983 (Box 1128, Folder 7610)
    - Scholars - Mellor, J., 1977-1980, 1982 1984, 1991 (Box 1128, Folder 7611)
    - Scholars - Mendel, W., 1977 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1128, Folder 7612)
    - Scholars - Mercier, E., 1977-1982, 1984 1992-1994 (Box 1128, Folder 7613)
    - Scholars - Meserve, W., 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 1128, Folder 7614)
    - Scholars - Mitchell, H., 1977-1982 (Box 1128, Folder 7615)
    - Scholars - Moore, G., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 1129, Folder 7616)